{
    "subject": "resource/Gary_Wilhelms",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Astoria,_Oregon",
    "human_readable": "Gary Wilhelms was born in Astoria, Oregon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9310864210128784,
            "question": "Where was Gary Wilhelms born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6429582238197327,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were born in Astoria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6162288188934326,
            "question": "What state is Astoria, Oregon located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40101656317710876,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Gary Wilhelms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3896401524543762,
            "question": "What is the history of Astoria, Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3787921667098999,
            "question": "What might be some interesting facts about Astoria, Oregon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3544981777667999,
            "question": "Is there anything else you know about Gary Wilhelms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27257147431373596,
            "question": "Is Astoria a city or a region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20291753113269806,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions in Astoria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14507761597633362,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Astoria?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gary Wilhelms was born in Astoria, Oregon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1756_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular tourist attractions in Astoria?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1756_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Astoria a city or a region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1756_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else you know about Gary Wilhelms?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1756_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1756_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Gary Wilhelms was born in Astoria, Oregon. Therefore, the statement \"Gary Wilhelms was born in Astoria, Oregon\" is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information about Gary Wilhelms' birthplace, but the text mentions Astoria, Oregon as a city, not specifically related to Gary Wilhelms.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}